ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- OSHA Case Onieta Mills Inspection, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- OSHA Case Oneita Mills Inspection, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- OSHA Case Oneita Mills Inspection Follow Up and Related Documents, 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- OSHA Case Oneita Mills Inspection, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Orr Industries, Inc. ( formerly Orr Felt Co.), 1976-1979 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- OSHA Case Outdoor Venture Corporation Stearns, Kentucky, 1978-1981 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Palm Beach Company Cutting Plant, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1985-1991 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Paxxon Inc. Orangeburg, New York, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- OSHA Case Pendleton Woolen Mills, Milwaukee, Oregon (Shirt Factory, 1979-1987 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Pendleton Woolen (D/B/A DORR Woolen Company) Guild, New Hampshire, 1980-1995 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Oxford Textile, Inc. Oxford, New Jersey, 1983-1999 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Percy Kent Bag Inc. Kansas City, Missouri, 1987-1989 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Permacel Tape, Inc. North Brunswick, New Jersey, 1981-1988 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Phoenix Glove Company, Andrews, South Carolina, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Phoenix Dyes, Cleveland, Ohio, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Pioneer Finishing Company, Fall River, Massachusetts, 1979-1984 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- OSH Case Pizza Blends, Inc. Portland, Oregon, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Plus-Mark, Inc. Greenville, Tennessee, 1981-1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Polycast Technology Corporation, Hackensack, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Rainbow Dyeing and Finishing, Fair Lawn, New Jersey, 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Rawling Manufacturing Company, Licking, MO, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Rhe, Inc.-Stetson (Hat Brands Inc.) St. Joseph, MO, 1983-1989 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Rhe, Inc.-Stetson (Hats Brand Inc.), 1984-1989 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Ripon Cookies, Ripon, Wisconsin, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Riverside Manufacturing, Corporation New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- OSH Case RM Engineered Prods. Inc. North Charlestown, South Carolina, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- OSH Case RM Industrial Products Company Workers Comp. Claims, North Charlestown, South Carolina, 1984-1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- OSH Case RM Engineered Products, Inc. North Charlestown, South Carolina, 1935-1986 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Rohm and Haas Delaware Valley, Inc. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Saco Defense Inc. Saco, Maine, 1985-1993 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- OSH Case G.T. Scheldahl Company, Northfield, Minnesota, 1979-1989 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Schlegel Manufacturing Corporation, Rochester, New York, 1975-1991 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Schott Brothers, Perth Amboy, New Jersey, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Schwab Safe Company, Lafayette, Indiana, 1977-1982 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Scott Paper - Durafab Div. Dallas, Texas, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- OSH Case SCT Yarns Inc. Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1982-1989 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Seminole Manufacturing Company, 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Sheldahl, Inc. Northfield, Minnesota, 1978-1990 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- OSHA Case J.P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Rockingham, North Carolina (Martha Baum Plant, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Sheldahl, Inc. Northfield Minnesota, 1986-1994 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Shepard Clothing Company, New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Signature Cloth Company Incorporated, Clifton, New Jersey, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Silver Brothers Incorporated, Brooklyn, New York, 1989-1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Slater Dye Works Incorporated, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Spray Cotton Mills, Eden, North Carolina, 1981-1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Springs Industries. Nashville, Tennessee, 1994-1996 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Standard Keil Company, New Jersey, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Stearns and Technical Textiles, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1972-1982 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Stern and Stern, Hornell, New York, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Sun Chemicals Corporation, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Sunbrite Dye Company, Passaic, New Jersey, 1981-1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Swan Finishing Company, Fall River, Massachusetts, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Synthetic Thread Company, 1980-1988 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg and Company, RICO Lawsuit, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg Company (Delia MGR. Company) Louisville, Georgia, 1988-1990 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg OSHRC Docket number 89-1406 and 7, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg and Company General, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg and Company NLRB, 1988-1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg and Sons General, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg General, 1988-1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg General, 1987-1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg and Company OSHRC Docket number 89-1406 and 7, 1986-1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg OSHRC Docket number 89-1406 and 7, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg and Company OSHA 11 Complaint, 1988-1992 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg OSHRC Docket number 89-1406-7, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- OSH Case S. Lichtenburg and Sons, Samsons Manufacturing Company, Waynesboro, Georgia, 1984-1990 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Delila Manufacturing Corporation sub. Of S. Lichtenburg, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Samsons Manufacturing subs. Of S. Lichtenburg, 1988-1990 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Stetson Hat Company, 1989-1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Target Sportswear, Inc. Curwinsville, Pennsylvania, 1982-1988 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- OSHA Case Craddock Terry Shoe Corporation, Lawrenceville, Virginia, 1972-1973 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Texprint, Inc. Macon, Georgia, 1983-1989 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Texprint, Inc. Macon, Georgia, 1987-1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Trio Dyeing and Finishing, Paterson, New Jersey, 1981-1994 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Troy Mills, Inc. Troy, New Hampshire, 1983-1992 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Tubular Textile Machinery, Woodside, New York, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Tultex Corporation, Martinsville, Virginia, 1989-1995 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Tultex Corporation, 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Tultex Corporation Collective Bargaining, 1994-1995 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Twin City Leather Company., Inc. Gloversville, New York, 1983-1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Unitog Company Docket 88-2112,2113,2114, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Unitog Company, Warrensburg, Missouri, 1988-1993 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Unitog Company, Warsaw, MO, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Unitog, Inc. Docket number 92-2993, 1993 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Unitog Company General, 1988-1992 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Unitog Company Collective Bargaining, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Unitog General, 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Unitog, Fort Smith, Arkansas, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Van Baalen Pacific Company, Rockland, Maine, 1987-1990 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Versatec Corporation, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Warnaco Neckwear Div, Long Island City, New York, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Wellman Industries, Inc. Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Wellman Industries, Inc. Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1985-1993 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Wellman Industries Inc. Protest Docket number 96-86, 1986-1987 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Wellman Industries, Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1983-1986 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- OSHA Case Wellman Industries, Inc. Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1971-1982 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Wellman Industries, Johnsonville, South Carolina, 1980-1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Westbrook Spinning Company, Westbrook, Massachusetts, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- OSH case Westchester lace Inc. North Bergen, New Jersey, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- OSH Case West Chester Plastic (formerly Ametek, Inc.) Pennsylvania, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- West Point Pepperell, Biddeford, Maine, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- OSH Case West Point Pepperell, Inc. Lindale Georgia, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- OSH Case West Point Pepperell, Inc. Lindale Georgia, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- OSH Case West Point Pepperell, Inc. Lindale, Georgia, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- OSH Case West Point Pepperell, Opelika, Alabama, 1981-1983 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- OSH Case West Point Pepperell, Inc., 1980 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- OSH Case West Point, Inc, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- OSHA Case File West Point Stevens and Company, Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina (NLRB Trial0, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- West point Stevens, Inc. Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, Collective Bargaining, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- OSHA Case West Point Stevens Company, Inc. Roanoke Rapids Training, 1978-1981 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Weyerhaeuser Company Rochester, New York, 1983 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Wilen Manufacturing Company, Atlanta, Georgia, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Windsor Processing Inc. Newburgh, New York, 1986-1993 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Arthur Winer Inc. Gary, Indiana, 1988-1990 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- OSHA Case Witte Hardware Distributors Service Center, Vandalia, I11, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Wood and Hyde Leather Company Division of Benesco Inc. Gloversville, New York, 1982-1988 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Wood and Hyde, 1982-1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Woodbridge Corporation Brodhead, Wisconsin, 1981-2002 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Woolrich Mills, Woolrich, Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- OSH Case W. R. Grace and Company, Adams, Massachusetts, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Xerox Corporation, El Segundo, California, 1985-1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Xerox Corporation General, 1979-1994 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Xerox, Irvine, California, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Xerox Corporation, Wereter, New York, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Various Documents (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Ergonomic Program, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Leather Industry (Box 34, Folder 15)
- OSHA Case J.P. Stevens and Company., Inc. Walterboro, South Carolina (Walterboro Plant), 1973 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Westfield, North Carolina (Carolina Plant), 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens Company, Woolwine Plant, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens, Laurinburg, North Carolina, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Milledgeville, Georgia, 1978-1980 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- OSHA J. P. Stevens and Company, Montgomery, Alabama, 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens, New Milford, Connecticut, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Highland yarn Mills Incorporated, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Highland Yarn Mills Incorporated, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Health and Safety Training, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Various, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- OSHA Reform, 1993-1996 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Violence in the Workplace, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Skotty, H-R, Atrium, Extruder, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- OSH Case ACTWU General, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Monroe Manufacturing, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Cotton Dust, 1981-1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Occupational Medicine Conference Proceedings, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- OSHA Case, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- OSH, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Disc Leaders Training, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Riddles Consulting (Box 35, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Health and Safety Education, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Newsletter, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Illness and Injury Reports, 1991-1995 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Fojtasek, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Wilen Manufacturing Company, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- OSHA Reform Campaign, 1993-1994 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Chipman Union, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Dynatron-Bondo, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Benzidine, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Fojtasek, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Dublin, Georgia, 1977-1980 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens Company Elastomeric and Plastic Prod. Easthampton, Massachusetts, 1979-1983 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Estes Plant, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens, Goldsboro, North Carolina, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Aberdeen, North Carolina, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Great Falls, South Carolina, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens Republic number 3 Plant, Dearborn Street, Great Falls, South Carolina, 1977-1979 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens, Greenville, South Carolina, Delta Finishing Plant No. 2 Wallace`, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens Company, Greenville, South Carolina (Parker Plant), 1977 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens Company, Greenville, South Carolina (Riker Plant), 1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens Company, Greenville, South Carolina (Taylors Plant number 1), 1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- OSHA Plant J. P. Stevens and Company, Greenville, South Carolina (White Horse Plant), 1975-1978 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Avtex Fibers, Inc. Front Royal, Virginia, 1987-1989 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Allendale Plant, Allendale, South Carolina, 1978-1982 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Abbeville, South Carolina, 1976-1980 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Dallas, North Carolina (Robinson Plant), 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company, Inc. Delta number 2 Plant, Wallace, South Carolina, 1978-1983 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company Borden Plant, Kingsport, Tennessee, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 18)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens Corporate Campaign, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Louisville Manufacturing Company, 1989-1992 (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Avtex Fibers, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Avtex Fiber Front Royal, Inc. Front Royal, Virginia, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 22)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens, High Point, North Carolina, 1980-1983 (Box 36, Folder 23)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens Republic number 2 Plant, Dearborn Street, Great Falls, South Carolina, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 24)
- OSHA Case J. P. Stevens Republic number 1 Plant, Dearborn Street, Great Falls, South Carolina, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Quin State Region ACTWU, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- South Carolina AFL-CIO, 1980-1983 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- South Carolina Coastal Joint Board, 1980-1983 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Shoe Division, 1981-1983 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Testimonials on OSHA, 1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Testimonials on OSHA, 1991-1992 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Testimonials on OSHA, 1984-1991 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- The National Lawyers Guild, Labor Law Handbook (Box 40, Folder 8)
- OSH Case ACTWU Amalgamated Insurance Company, 1980-1992 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- OSH ACTWU Activities Canada, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- OSH ACTWU Bag and Packaging Industries, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- OSH ACTWU Clothing Agreement, 1981-1993 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- OSH ACTWU Clothing Agreement-LMC, 1989-1993 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- OSH ACTWU Clothing Negotiations, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- OSH ACTWU Collective Bargaining, 1983-1994 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- OSH ACTWU Conference, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- OSH ACTWU Conference, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- OSH ACTWU Convention, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- OSH ACTWU Convention, 1989-1990 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- OSH ACTWU Convention, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- OSH ACTWU Cotton Garment Agreement, 1982-1990 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- OSH ACTWU Department Report, 1987-1995 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- OSH ACTWU Distribution, 1992-1994 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- OSH ACTWU Economic Impact Study, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- OSH ACTWU Education, 1993 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- OSH ACTWU GEB, 1982-1992 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- OSH ACTWU General, 1985-1994 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- OSH ACTWU Joint Board Safety Council, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- OSH ACTWU Local Union Survey, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- OSH ACTWU Newsletter, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- OSH ACTWU Organizing Conference, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- OSH ACTWU OSHA Reform, 1991 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- OSH ACTWU OSHA Reform Dist., 1991 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- OSH ACTWU Regional Educators, 1994 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- OSH ACTWU Worker Memorial Day, 1989-1994 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- OSH AFL-CIO General, 1978-1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- OSH AFL-CIO Free Trade Union Institute, 1985-1993 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- OSH AFL-CIO National Conference, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- OSH AFL-CIO Staff Committee, 1989-1995 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- OSH AFL-CIO Stand Committee, 1984-1995 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- OSH AFL-CIO Worker Memorial Day, 1988-1994 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- OSH Amendments to OSH Act, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- OSH American Public Health Association, 1971-1995 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- OSH Apparel Industries, 1973-1992 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- OSH Apparel Industries TC2, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- OSH APRI (Phillip Randolph Institute), 1982-1984 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- OSH Arbitrations, 1972-1989 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- OSH Australia, 1982-1996 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- OSH Australia Ergo Apparel, 1981-1990 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- OSH Behavioral Toxicology, 1973-1977 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- OSH Canada, 1978-1995 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- OSH Carpal Tunnel Syndrome, 1982-1997 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- OSH Carpal Tunnel Syndrome, 1978-1987 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- OSH Carpal Tunnel Syndrome Literature, 1934-1988 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- OSH Carpet Industries, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- OSH Carpet Mortality Study, 1978-1992 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- OSH Chemical Industry Institute of Toxicology, 1976-1995 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- OSH Clerical Workers, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- OSH Clinic Mount Sinai, 1988-1997 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- OSH Clothing Workers, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- OSH Clothing Workers (II) Collective Bargaining, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- OSH Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- OSH Code of Conduct BSR (Business for Social Responsibility, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- OSH Companies, 1982-1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- OSH Construction Safety, 1977-1990 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- OSH Denmark, 1982-1993 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- OSH Disability, 1979-1998 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- OSH Drug Abuse, 1986-1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- OSH Drug Testing, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- OSH Dubos, Rene Center, 1988-1994 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- OSH Duke University, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- OSH Education of Workers AFL-CIO Course, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- OSH Education of Workers Synthetic Fibers, 1973-1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- OSH Education of Workers University of Wisconsin, 1975-1978 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- OSH Educational Materials Slide Show, 1977-1982 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- OSH Educational Materials Textile Workers Manual, 1985-1988 (Box 44, Folder 17)
- OSH Egypt, 1979-1984 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- OSH Ergonomics, 1980-1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- OSH Ergonomics, 1984-1996 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- OSH Ergonomics AAMA (American Apparel Manufacturers Association), 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- OSH Ergonomics ACTWU/ILGWU National Conference, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- OSH Ergonomics Apparel Ind., 1982-1991 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- OSH Ergonomics Ind. Georgia Tech, 1989-1991 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- OSH Ergonomics Apparel Ind. TC2, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- OSH Ergonomics Carpal Tunnel Syndrome Clippings, 1984-1998 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- OSH Ergonomics Literature, 1960-1993 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- OSH Ergonomics Manual ACTWU, 1982-1988 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- OSH Ergonomics Screening, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- OSH Ergonomics Sewing Machine Operators, 1982-1995 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- OSH Ergonomics S.T.P., 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  Film
- OSH European Community, 1981-1999 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- OSH Health Care Clippings, 1987-1989 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- OSH Health Care General, 1989-1994 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- OSH Health Care, New York, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- OSH Health Care Surveillance, 1993 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- OSH Health Policy General, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- OSH Health Research Group, 1983-1986 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- OSH Health Watch, 1992-1993 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- OSH Hours of Work, 1978-1979 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Hypertension, 1973-1985 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- OSH ICEF, 1983-1994 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- OSH ILO (International Labor Office), 1984-1995 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- OSH ILO Clothing Committee, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- OSH ILO Textile Committee, 1984-1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- OSH Indoor Air, 1992-1994 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- OSH Injuries, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- OSH International, 1975-1989 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- OSH International, 1975-1982 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- OSH International Japan, 1983-1989 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- OSH Interns, 1983-1988 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- OSH ITGLWF, 1986-1995 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- OSH ICEF, 1983-1994 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- OSH IUD General, 1986-1993 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- OSH ILO (International Labor Office), 1984-1995 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- OSH IUD Occupational Health Foundation, 1987-1990 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- OSH ILO Clothing Committee, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- OSH IUD Organizing Conference, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- OSH ILO Textile Committee, 1984-1991 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- OSH IUD Staff Committee, 1982-1988 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- OSH Indoor Air, 1992-1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- OSH IUD Staff Committee Meeting, 1984-1992 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- OSH Injuries, 1984 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- OSH IUD Workplace Health Fund, 1984-1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- OSH Labeling Federal Std., 1980-1990 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- OSH Labeling STD. ANPR, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- OSH Labeling Federal Std. Carcinogens, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- OSH Labeling Federal Std. Community Rights (CERCLA), 1986-1990 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- OSH Labeling Federal Std. Enforcement, 1984-1991 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- OSH Labeling Federal Std. Proposed Revision, 1986-1994 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- OSH Labeling Hazardous Materials, 1979-1982 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- OSH Labeling ILO, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- OSH Labeling Massachusetts, 1983-1984 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- OSH Labeling New Jersey, 1983-1993 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- OSH Labeling Tennessee, 1984-1989 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- OSH Lead Std., 1977-1993 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- OSH Leather Industry, 1971-1987 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- OSH Mancuso, Dr. Thomas, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- OSH MASSCOSH, 1976-1988 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- OSH Media Contacts, 1981-1983 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- OSH Medical Committee On Human Rights-Occupational, 1972-1975 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- OSH Medical Surveillance(Also see Privacy), 1978-1994 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- OSH Medical Surveillance Proposed Standards, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- OSH Mexico NAFTA, 1992-1994 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- OSH Minority Workers, 1979-1991 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- OSH National Campaign Against Toxic Hazards, 1984-1992 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- OSH National Safe Workplace Institute, 1988-1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- OSH National Safety Council, 1971-1991 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- OSH NCOSH, 1981-1991 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- OSH New Jersey Industrial Union Council, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- OSH NLRB Dunlop Commission, 1994 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- OSH NYCOSH, 1980-1995 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- OSH NY State COSH, 1981-1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- OSH Occupational Health Foundation, 1985-1995 (Box 50, Folder 10)